to
live I said welcome brothers and sisters
to another WS a question and answer will
we open up with the Ten Commandments
that God commanded the whole world to
keep brother tzel and God spake all
these words saying I am the Lord thy God
which have brought thee out of the land
of Egypt out of the house of bondage
thou shall have no other gods before me
thou not make into thee any image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for why the Lord thy God
am a jealous God visiting the iniquities
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me and showing Mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my Commandments thou shall not take take
the name of the Lord thy God in vain for
the Lord will not hold him Guiltless
that taketh his name in vain remember
the Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shall thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God and it thou shall not do
any work thou nor thy son nor thy
daughter thy man servant nor that maid
servant nor thy cattle nor th stranger
that is within thy gates for six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefor the Lord bless the
Sabbath day and holiday honor thy father
and thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee thou shall not kill thou sh
not commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou sh not bear false witness against
thy neighbor thou shall not cover thy
neighbor's house thou not cover thy
neighbor's wife no his man sir
nor his ma servant nor his Ox nor his
ass nor anything that is that Naes we
read that rad Exodus 21 through1 17 and
may the Lord have a blessing to the
reading of his word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep it mind that
all B questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life and we asking that you keep those
questions to us two scripture minimum so
let me introduce the family that's on
the panel we got brother Julius good
evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother Jerome rest in peace
Brother tanzel good evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have sister Casey with us
and the guest caller and I'm brother
Cornell sister Deborah what's our first
question of the evening yes there are
several Q&A questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so Israelite Gil says can
someone help with with first corini 11
verse 16 when Paul said there is no such
custom all right sure someone can help
let's go to that First Corinthians
um
11 and pick it up we're going to pick it
up at that one and two because at verse
16 Paul was letting it be known that hey
that um anybody that doubts God he
didn't have no such custom dealing with
that and we'll tell you in the scripture
why Paul said that but let's go to 1
Corinthians
11 and when you get there brotherr read
that verse one and two for me
go ahead be ye followers of me even as I
also am of Christ uhhuh now I Praise You
Brethren that you remember me in all
things and keep the ordinance as I
deliver them to you so Paul is saying
here to be ye followers of me even also
as he was of Christ because he went
around and taught nothing but the truth
and he gave that word that was given
from one Shepherd and he said and he
taught to keep all the ordinances that
he was going around teaching all the
people to keep skip down to verse 16 go
ahead but if any man seem to be
contentious we have no such custom
neither the Churches of God but if any
man seem to be contentious if he doubt
God hey Paul said we don't have no
custom like that because everybody that
was going around preaching that true
word of God didn't have no doubt about
the God that Paul was preaching about
and the god that We Believe on this
panel turn back to First Corinthians the
2 chapter 1 Corinthians 2 because Paul
knows all about
Jesus First
Corinthians the 2
chapter and let's see who Paul was
preaching about fig it up at verse one
brother go
ahead and I Brethren when I came to you
came not with Excellency of speech or of
wisdom declaring unto you the testimony
of God uhhuh I determined not to know
anything among you save Jesus Christ and
him crucified oh so Paul say hey he he
came preaching nothing about Jesus
Christ and him they crucified skip down
to verse four and go ahead and my speech
and my preaching was not with enticing
words of man's Wisdom uh demonstration
of the spirit and of power uhhuh that
your faith should not stand in the
wisdom of men but in the power of God
and that's why you can't doubt God when
you know his true word and you are
applying it unto your life read 12 and
13 for
me now we have received not the spirit
of the world but the spirit which is of
god we might know the things that are
freely given to us of God
with things we Al also we speak not in
The Words which man wisdom teacheth but
which the Holy Ghost teacher comparing
spiritual things with spiritual so Paul
was letting it be known exactly where he
was getting that word from and he said
and he came not in The Words which man
wisdom was about but which the Holy
Ghost teacheth comparing spiritual
things with spiritual here a little
there a little and there you will find
the true word word of God when you got a
true Pastor or teacher to lead you right
and that's all I got on
that and we hope that that answered your
question there as we continue to move on
to our next question moving on dot
Martin asks I'm
aaden Satan being put in Chains and
Jesus feet touching the Mount of Olives
are these three things
happening at the first coming of the
Lord so Jerome can you share some light
on these three things that they question
about yeah th those three things um
don't have anything to do with the first
coming of the Lord because the first
coming of the Lord was about him coming
in the flesh and to uh die for the sins
of man okay but
Armageddon um say being in Chains
putting chains and Jesus feet hitting a
Mount of Olives that's more centered
around um the second coming of the Lord
now the Armageddon actually kind of
takes place before the before the Lord
come but not not too much further from
the coming of the the second coming of
the Lord so let's go look at it uh let's
go to Revelation 16 pick it up at the 12
when you get it go ahead and
read and the sixth Angel poured out his
vow upon the Great River euphies and the
waters thereof was dried up that the way
of the kings of the East might be
prepared and I saw three unclean spirits
like frogs come out of the mouth of the
dragon and out of the mouth of the Beast
out of the mouth of the false prophet
but they are the spirits of devil
working miracles which go forth unto the
kings of the earth and of the whole
world to gather them to the battle of
the great day of God Almighty yeah and
this battle this battle is is this
Armageddon that you talking about they
the Nations uh Kings of the East and the
kings of the West and all of the Allies
on both sides they going to be gathered
to this battle you know
and before the Lord come they going to
be doing what they doing as far as they
fighting one another and then they gonna
realize they got a bigger problem at the
coming of the Lord you know then they
gonna stop fighting one another and
fight the Lord okay but keep
reading behold I come as a thief so
bless is he that watches and keepeth his
garments lest he walk naked and they see
ashamed verse 16 and he gathered them
together into a place called in the
Hebrew tongue
armag uhhuh and then
17 and the Seven Angel poured out his
bow into the air and there came a great
voice out of the Temple of Heaven from
the throne saying it is done yeah so you
know there seven trumpet that's going to
bring the Lord and they gonna fight
against the Lord and we know who gonna
win that battle so uh then you talked
about uh Jesus uh
feet hitting that uh Mount of Olives you
can read about that in Zechariah 14 so
that that is at the coming of the lord
we don't have to go there but you can
read Zechariah 14 and it talks about him
coming to to do battle with those that
going to be gathered for this Armageddon
okay and then uh Satan being put in
Chains that's at that's at the coming of
the Lord too because the Lord is going
to be the one that have him
thrown uh in the
pit okay so that's at the coming of the
Lord too all right so hopefully that
answer your question so brother Jerome
it is the second coming not the first
yes all right thank you for that hope
that that answered their question as we
continue to move on to our next yeah she
also asked in Genesis 3: 22 how could
man have eaten from the Tree of Life in
the garden and live forever after he had
sinned was man Immortal in the
garden all right brother Drake can you
share some light on that question yes
let's go to Genesis 3 and we'll read
verses 22-
24 and that will answer your question
go ahead brother tanzel when you get it
go ahead and the Lord God said behold
the man has become as one of us to know
good and evil and now lest he put forth
his hand and take also of the tree of
life and eat and live
forever therefore the Lord God sent him
forth from the Garden of Eden to till
the ground from which he was taken so he
drove out the m and he placed at the
east of the garden of Eden cherubs and a
flaming sword which turned every way to
keep the way of the tree of life we see
here that man did not eat of the tree of
life and live forever and he is not
Immortal at this time let's go to 1
Corinthians 15 and we just G to read
verse 53 1 Corinthians 15 and 53 read
that when you get it
brother First Corinthians 15
yes sir
53 for this corruptible must put on
incorruption and this Mortal must put on
immortality uhuh so when this
corruptible shall have put on
incorruption and this Mortal shall have
put on
immortality then shall be brought to
pass the same that is written death is
swallowed up in Victory so let's look at
when this is going to happen read verse
50 50 uh 51 to 52 go ahead
brother behold I show you a mystery we
should not all sleep but we shall all be
changed in a moment in the twinkling of
an eye at the last Trump for the trumpet
shall sound and the dead shall be raised
Incorruptible and we shall be changed
and that is when man will have an
Incorruptible body at the last Trum
Jerome just talked about that when man
is raised out of the Grave right I hope
it
helps all right brother thank you for
that as we continue to move on to our
next question yes our last question for
you is to explain Ephesians 4: 7 and
8 Ephesians 47 and 8 Why Don't We Go
There
tzel Ephesians 4 7 and
eight and why don't you pick it up at
that seven and the guest caller will
take it from
there but unto every one of us is given
Grace according to the measure of the
gift of
Christ wherefore he said when he
ascended up on high he led the Captivity
the captiv captive and gave gifts unto
men
so what really happen this this grace
that God gave us for the check and
chance of immortality in other
words Adam when he sinned against us
against God he took that away from him
and then we was under a death sentence
Point Blank we couldn't get out from it
out from under it let's go into Hebrews
second
chapter and saw what Jesus had to do to
uh uh uh get this death Sinners up off
us Hebrews 2 and9 then we're going to
skip and read 14 and
15 read it when you get there but we see
Jesus who was made a little lower than
the angels for the suffering of death
crowned with Glory and Honor that he by
the grace of God should taste death for
every
man okay so now when he had when he died
he took
death off man and do mean that man man
have to everybody is given to Die the
first time but it's the it's the second
death that man have to get away from and
what we was always afraid of so when he
died that took death skip down to verse
um
14 and 15 and read it for as much then
as the children are partakers of Flesh
and Blood he also himself likewise took
part of the same that through death he
might destroy him that had the power of
death that is the
devil and deliver them who
th go ahead and deliver them who through
fear of death were all their lifetime
subject to
bondage so now when he died he delivered
us that was always subject to bondage
bondage of what of death so what he did
was he took death away death was what he
led captive now let's go quickly to
First Corinthians 15th chapter and read
verse 21 and
22 read when you get there for it says
by Man Came Death by man came also the
resurrection of the
Dead for as an Adam all died even so in
Christ shall all be made
alive now so Adam brought
death Jesus came and took it up office
so they're letting you know that he led
death captive wherein death had us under
captivity quickly to Zechariah the 9th
chapter read verses 9 and
11 when you get
there 9 9 and 11
as for thee also by the blood of thy
Covenant I have sent forth thy prisoners
out of the pit wherein is no water turn
ye to the stronghold ye prisoners of
Hope now make sure make sure we read uh
uh see who this is go back and read
verse 9 chap uh Zechariah 9 and verse 9
then skip down to verse 11 so we'll know
who we're talking about here who did
what
Zechariah 9 and pick it up at verse
n Rejoice greatly oh Daughter of Zion
shout oh daughter of Jerusalem Behold
thy King cometh unto thee he is just and
having salvation lowly and riding upon
an ass and upon a coat the F of an
ass so skip down to verse 11 now and
read it
again as for thee also by the blood of
thy Covenant I have sent forth thy
prisoners out of the pit wherein is no
water so he had to come and let you know
that pit represent if you're in in a pit
with no water you going to die it all
comes down to one thing we was captive
under death Jesus came and he took death
of office and that's that's uh uh
oh and that's what it's telling telling
you that he led captivity captive
because we was captive under the death
sentence and so then he said he gave
gifts to men the second part of that
let's go and see what the gifts out as
it go back to Ephesians the 4th
chapter and read verse 10 and 11
Ephesians 4: 10 and
11 he that descended is the same also
that us send it up far above all Heavens
that he might feel all
things and he gave some Apostles and
some prophets and some evangelists and
some pastors and
teachers for the perfecting of
the Finish see this is what he did he he
that's the gift he left he left people
here that could teach you how to take
advantage of this grace that he had
teach in the
word so now he took death of off you but
you had to be taught how to take care
how to take advantage of it and what he
did he left you these people with your
gifts from God to man to teach us how to
take advantage of this new Freedom that
we had after the Lord let us out under
the pit in other words let us out under
death sentence so you have to do that
through Grace what is Grace gave you a
free gift and then you have to do
through faith you have to believe that
Jesus did it and then you obey his voice
that he is going to send you by way of
of a uh you know prophets by way of
Apostles by way of evangelist
and pastors and teachers all of these
guys are people that informs you on the
word of God that you might take
advantage of this G uh uh free guilt by
knowing what to do and obeying it that's
all I have to say all right hope that
answers your question and we thank God
for his great Mercy all right sister
Deborah next
question next question Ben Elf asks do
we know how old Esau was when he was
exiled do we know brother Julius no we
don't the word Exile means to be banned
uh to be banned or expelled from your
own country we don't know the book don't
say I've never read it where the book
gave her age of Esau being exiled out of
his own
country okay hope that ansed your
question there next question next
question Ben F also asked in Matthew
25:
32-34 and
41 are there other scriptures elsewhere
in the Bible that also symbolize the
sheep that will inherit the kingdom and
the goats that shall inherit the Lake of
Fire I'm curious about the reference to
goats and
sheep all right we ask brother Julius
some light on these goats and on these
sheep let's see what the book say let's
go to let's go to the scripture let's go
to Matthew
25 it just represents peoples it depends
upon the context in which it's
used Jesus is called the Lamb of God in
John but in Leviticus he's called the
goat but and then he's even called a
scapegoat but in this context here we're
talking about the wicked and the
righteous the Sheep repres represent the
righteous and the Goat represents the
wicked but it's primarily here in
Matthew the 25th chapter when you get it
my brother pick it up at verse 32 and go
ahead start at verse
31 well the son of man shall come in his
glory and all the Holy Angels with him
then shall he sit upon the throne of his
glory so now we talking about the return
of the Lord with his rewards go ahead
and before him shall be gathered all
Nations nations are peoples go ahead and
he shall separate them one from another
as a Shepherd divided his sheep from the
goats and he shall set the sheep on his
right hand that's the righteous go ahead
the
left and the goats on the left skip down
read 34 go ahead then shall the king say
unto them on his right hand Come Ye
blessed of my father inherit the Kingdom
prepared for you from the foundation of
the
world and that's the reward of the
righteous or what the book called
symbolizes as the Lord's
sheep read verse
41 then shall he say also unto them of
the left hand depart from me ye curse
and the Everlasting fire prepare for the
devil and his angels so now that's the
wicked you could read scriptures certain
like they might not call them sheeps and
goats but you can go to Revelation where
the Lord going to give his the righteous
uh uh the kingdom of God and then the
wicked going into the Lake of Fire which
represents the goat but in this primary
context here in Matthew is talking
about the PE peoples Nations represented
by sheeps and goats right that's all I
got I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
brother let's move to our next question
sister
uh yes Malik Shakur uh
says uh could you explain Genesis 3
verses 14 and 15 if the serpent is a
person why was he cursed above every
beast and why did he say thy belly
should thou go all right Malik we just
want to inform you that we answered that
exact question last week on July the
10th 24
at 26 minutes and 7 Seconds of our show
so you can go in there and you can
review that and that was a question that
the guest caller had answered so we hope
that you'll visit that and thank you our
next question yes Miss Wade asked in
Isaiah 58 verse
63 excuse me Isaiah 58 verse 13 what do
this mean not to speak your own words on
the
Sabbath not speaking your own words on
the Sabbath Dre can you share some light
yes sir let's go to uh Isaiah 58 and
read verse
13 read it brother when you get it if
thou turn away thy foot from the Sabbath
from doing thy pleasure on my holy day
and call the Sabbath of delight the holy
of the Lord honorable and shall honor
him not doing thy own work ways nor
finding thy own pleasure nor speaking
thy own words right so you know it's
it's talking about your regular
Pleasures that you find during the week
or anything else are speaking your own
words let's go look at that in a couple
of other places first Peter 4 and
11 speaking your own words is is really
just self-explanatory this is the Lord s
AB day but uh first Peter 4 and read
verse 11 brother when you get it go
ahead if any man speak let him speak as
the Oracles of
God if any man Minister let him do it as
of the ability which God give that God
in all things may be glorified through
Jesus Christ to whom be praise and
Dominion forever and ever amen you doing
this this on the Sabbath day he said
I'mma feed you with the heritage of
Jacob he going to bless you you going to
edify people you gonna speak the Oracles
of god let's go to one more place let's
go to Ephesians 4 and we gonna read just
one verse there verse
29 Ephesians 4 and 29 and when you get
that go ahead and read it
brother let no corrupt communication
proceed out of your mouth for that which
is good to the use of edifying that it
may Minister Grace unto the hearers yeah
so this is something that you can do
every day it's not exclusive to the
Sabbath but on the Sabbath day
especially if you not speaking your own
words don't use corrupt
communication but use good words to the
use of edifying that it may Minister
Grace onto the hearers so I hope that
that answers your question
yes sir brother Dre keeping in mind the
Lord said that's a holy day yes sir
let's do it the best we can thank you
for that brother hope that answered that
question next question sister next
question Stephen googus asked is one
hour of the Lord's time three and a half
years of our time since the hour of
Temptation is three and a half years for
men for man so dealing with the hour and
the three and a half years can you share
some light on that question guest
caller I believe that's yours oh okay no
that's the guest
calling well well the Bible says what it
says uh that this uh beast and false
prophet going is going to uh rule for 3
and 1/2 years and the Lord called that
the Great Tribulation he said and it's
called the hour of Temptation now we
know the Lord called both of them the
same because if the hour of Temptation
is going to be carrying out by flesh and
blood men then it's talking about the
same
time Lord set the
time and that is three and a half years
of man's
time that's all I have to say all right
thank you for that as we continue to
move on to our next one with a time
check yes the time is 8:03 he also asked
in Matthew
23:9 it says we are to call no man Our
Father does this apply to our biological
father as well what are we to call our
biological fathers all right so when it
says it says we are to call no man Our
Father does this apply to our biological
father absolutely not when we go into to
this Matthew 23 we're talking about
spiritually on the religious Faith part
let's go and read that uh
Tanz and let's pick it up at verse one
and then we'll read down so we can see
who it is that like to go contrary to
the word of God um pick it up at there
verse
one Matthew 23 And1 go ahead my brother
then spake Jesus to the m to and to his
disciples saying the scribes and the
Pharisees sit in Moses seat uhhuh all
therefore whatsoever they B You observe
that observe and do but do not ye after
their Works they Lord saying go ahead
brother that was it okay so the Lord is
saying that we're not supposed to do
after the work of these guys here let's
see what they do skip down to that verse
six for me and let's see what else they
do go ahead and love
the upper most rooms at feast in the
chief SE hey tzel pick that up at verse
five for me I'm sorry pick it up at five
and read down this is something else
they like that the Lord talks about go
ahead but all their Works they do for it
to be seen of
men they br their pharies and they lost
the borders of their garments yes and
love the uppermost rooms at feast and
the chief seats in the synagogues uhhuh
they real special let them tell it go
ahead and greed in the Marcus and to be
called of men Rabbi Rabbi and like to be
called Rabbi and Rabbi another word for
that is Master you're not supposed to be
calling no man on this Earth Master go
ahead except for the Lord go
ahead and and be not ye called Rabbi for
one is your master even Christ and all
ye are Brethren that's right and call no
man your father upon the Earth for one
is your father which is in heaven and
call no man your father upon the Earth
and Lord was talking about on the
spiritual
side and don't call any man father go
ahead neither be ye called Masters for
one is your master even Christ and don't
even call the other the master for one
is your master even Christ so what is it
that you can call your biological father
hey you call him father you call him dad
you call him daddy you know so that's
all within order but on the spiritual
side hey you don't call no man father
right you don't call no man Rabbi and
you don't call no man Master but as far
as your biological then you can call him
Father Dad or daddy your stepfather hey
same applies to him you can call him
Father Dad or daddy also if y'all have
that type of relationship that's all I
got and we hope that that answers your
question we're gonna move on to our next
next one Israel asked in Romans 1
verse3 how was Christ made up of the
seed of David if there was a virgin
birth and Mary didn't have sex with
Joseph
up a small act for the Lord guest caller
can you share some light on
that well the whole thing is he he was
made of the seed of David because God
said he was going to come through the
seed of David that's right Romans let's
go to Romans the 1 chapter read verses 1
through3 but I want you to see what it
says Paul a servant of Jesus Christ
called to be an apostle
separated unto the gospel of God which
he had promised or for By His His
prophets in the Holy
scriptures concerning his son Jesus
Christ Our Lord which was made of the
seed of David according to the
flesh uhhuh but read read a little more
and declared to be the Son of God with
power according to the spirit of
Holiness by the resurrection from the
dead mhm okay so he was he was called
seed of
David because God said he was going to
do that that's why when you go into
Hebrews the 10th chapter he tell you
about animal sacrifice he said you
didn't said the blood of bulls and ghost
couldn't remove sin so a body has thou
uh uhh prepared prepar me yes took that
body on but but the first one the first
uh one whose seed that uh uh uh uh that
Jesus uh uh put on was
Abraham let's go into uh uh Hebrews the
2 chapter and look at
that let's see what we're going to read
of that Hebrews
2 uh
first let me see let's
see but Jesus made a little Lord in
angels verse
16 well we can we can read nine and then
we're going to skip now all
right read it when you get there but we
see Jesus who was made a little a little
lower than the angels for the suffering
of death crowned with Glory and Honor
that he by the grace of God should takes
death for every
man okay we had to have a body to do
that you had to have a flesh and blood
body skip down to verse 14 and go ahead
for as much then as the children are
partakers of Flesh and Blood he also
himself likewise took part of the same
that through death he might destroy him
that had the power of death that is the
devil it tell you that he took part of
the saint that mean that he took on his
body that was prepared through the
lineage of Abraham and David
right down right on down uh to verse 16
and read
it for very for verily he took not on
him the nature of angels but he took on
him the Seed of
Abraham and David come by way of
Abraham and that's why Jesus came down
through the lineage he put the body in
the in their lineage and uh I don't see
what that's too hard to do being that he
took dirt and created Created us out of
dirt
right so we have people that keep keep
thinking that uh uh Jesus had a
biological father well did Adam have a
biological father
nope then if he can do that with dirt he
can have a body prepared which he had
prepared like he said in Hebrews the
10th chapter a body has thou prepared me
and he prepared that body Jesus took it
over and the angel injected into the
woman's
womb I tell you I said you know you you
enclose me in my mother's
womb so God said it God said it then who
gonna dispute it
nobody right all right thank you for
that we hope that answers your question
next question next question Zion kq7 U
yss if we if we make it to the kingdom
will it be a need to eat s we will live
forever all right brother Jerome Shar
some light about um eating and living
forever in the
Kingdom yeah be so blessed to be become
a spirit
being at the um Resurrection you can eat
but you don't have a need to eat you
know and so I want to show you example
when Jesus uh came up on uh was
resurrected on the third day that he
prepared food and he
ate while he was a spirit being so let's
go to Luke
24 and pick it up at verse 36 read to 37
we're going to
skip that's Luke 34 Luke
24 okay and pick it up at verse 36 and
37 get it go ahead and read
and as they thus spake Jesus himself
stood in the midst of them and said unto
them peace be unto
you but they was terrified and the
fright and suppose that they had seen
the spirit yeah because at that point
Jesus had resurrected so he got his
Spirit body now skip down to verse 41
read to
43 and while they yet believed not for
joy and wondered he said unto them
have ye here any meat and they gave him
a piece of a bro fish and of a honeycomb
and he took it and did eat before them
yeah there it is that's all I got on all
right thank you there brother that was
some good light hope that answered their
question we moving on to our next yes
little mama Hayes asked is the of
Babylon all the Pagan goddesses
throughout history also she wants to
know is the Catholic church and
Pentecostal church under the same
umbrella brother Julius what you
say the answer is no and
yes the great let's go to Revelation the
17th chapter and let's answer that
question I'm going tell you why we said
no and yes because Babylon it depend on
what Babylon you're talking about the
series of Babylon but the original
Babylon by the hites but then you have
what we dealing with and disper to your
question Babylon the
great Revelation
1710 pick it up at verse
one go ahead and there came one of the
Seven Angels which had the seven vows
and talk with me saying unto me come
hither and I will show unto thee the
Judgment of the great that sth
upon many Waters now this great wh
represents a church show you what I'm
talking about uh skip down to verse four
and go ahead and the woman was arrayed
in purple and scarlet color and decked
with gold and precious stones and Pearls
having a golden cup in her hand full of
abomination and fil of her fornication
this is an exact depiction of the Roman
Catholic Church you know the the uh the
Cardinals wear red the scarlet and then
the bishop wear purple and then they had
that golden cup where they have
mass and look up but she's called a
great go ahead verse five and upon
her for here was a name written mystery
Babylon the great the mother of Harless
and Abomination of the earth she is a
mother church and she got a whole bunch
of churches under her umbrella
so she's a mystery because nobody knows
who she are who she is except the Lord
revealed it to us now she's mystery
Babylon we call it Western Europe or the
EU and under the EU they all have to
sign the treaties of Rome so therefore
this great represents the Western
uh should I say the Roman Catholic
church and yes to answer your second
question uh the Pentecostal church is
Under the Umbrella of she just under the
umbrella of protestantism but this also
that's why it said the mother of harlots
so protestantism all these other
churches come from under her why because
the Pentecostal church is going to
celebrate Christmas they're going to
celebrate Easter they're going to
believe in going to heaven when you die
and they're Gonna Worship On the first
day of the week all these churches does
is under protestantism but they are
under the umbrella of the mother church
I hope that helped anybody want to
add I think you hit it pretty good there
brother thank you for that answer hope
that answer that question as we move on
to our next yes just looking ask can you
explain First Timothy 2
verse4 did Adam sin First Timothy 2 and4
Dre what you say did Adam sin yes sir
Adam did let's go to 14 and read it two
first uh is it 1 Timothy 2:14 read that
brother
tanzel and Adam was not deceived but the
woman being deceived was in the
transgression uhhuh So Adam wasn't
deceived he knew what it was you know it
says in I think it's in James he say to
him that know to do a thing and doeth it
not to him it is sin that's right let's
go over to uh Romans the 5th chapter yes
sir Romans 5 and we just going to read
one verse there verse 12 Romans
5 go ahead when you get it brother
wherefore as by one man sin enter into
the world and death by sin and so death
pass upon all men for that all have
sinned you see it says by one man sin
into into the world let's go to 1
Corinthians 15
1 Corinthians 15: 21 and
22 go ahead when you get it
brother for Since By Man Came Death by
man came also the resurrection of the
dead or as in Adam all died even so in
Christ should all be made alive as an
Adam all died you know even so in Christ
shall all be made live and on your own
time you could read Romans
30:
10-16 how a husband can make void what a
woman
does so on your own you can read that
Romans 3010 and 16 so yes Adam
sin that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
and uh sister Deborah I believe we going
into new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for July the 17th
2024 Marcelino Reed asks or says in Joel
2 vers
28-32 and Acts 2 verse
17 are the scriptures indicating that
salvation is now for everyone as he
poured out his Spirit on All
Flesh brother Jerome what you
say first um let's go read those verses
and I think in those two verses that you
gave um you you're asking about that
spirit for one thing and that spirit is
the word but let's go read those two
verses Joel
28-32 let's read that you get it go
ahead and read
and it shall come to pass afterward that
I will pour out my spirit upon All Flesh
and your sons and your daughters shall
prophesies your old men shall dream
dreams your young men shall see
visions and also upon the servant and
upon the handmaid in those days will I
pour out my spirit and I will show
wonders in heaven and in the earth blood
and fire and pillars of smoke and the
sun shall be turned to Darkness and the
moon unto blood before the Great and the
terrible day of the Lord
come and it shall come to pass that
whosoever shall call on the name of the
Lord shall be delivered for in the Mount
Zion and in Jerusalem shall be
Deliverance as the Lord ha said and in
the remnant whom the Lord shall
call okay now before we go to that acts
I just want to say the Lord been pouring
out out his Spirit he was pouring out
his Spirit um way in the
garden when he was talking to
Adam he was pouring his Spirit out then
you know he told him don't talk to the
tree knowledge good and evil but the
tree of the uh life he said you can
freely eat and if you freely eating that
you getting that Spirit which is that
word you know so let's go uh read that
acts 2 and7 now
you get it go
ahead and it shall come to pass in the
last day said God I will put out of my
spirit upon All Flesh and your sons and
your daughters shall prophesize and your
young men shall see visions and your old
men your dream
Dreams yeah so go ahead me finish
it and on my service and on my handmaids
I will pour out and those days of my
spirit and they shall
prophesize and I will show wonders in
Heaven above and signs in the earth
beneath blood and fire and Vapors of
smoke yeah so even from the Garden of
Eden all the way into these verses that
you're reading the Lord is constantly
pouring out his spirit it's just that
man ain't listening don't care to listen
they're not retaining his word but you
got some of us out here that that's
hearing you know so
uh I had a verse in here but I think
that that answers the question if
anybody want to add something they
can all right yeah like you said brother
hey this word is for all nations
whosoever will let them come yes sir yes
sir all right sister de we're gonna move
on to our next question yes Ronda Assa
Robinson asked if I'm not able to attend
Sabbath Bible studies is it an
Abomination to our Lord Jesus Christ
will it Place us into the Lake of Fire I
watch and study on my own to grow in
knowledge all right well if you're not
able to attend the Sabbath Day Bible
study for whatever reason you know we
don't know um whether or not we may have
a church in your area or not but if
you're not able to
attend um and you continue to study with
us I think that's the best that you
could probably put forward right there
but as far as going into Lake of Fire
that's not our call we don't make that
call but if you're not able to attend um
then you just keep on studying and
worshiping with us because God has
blessed us with the words even of
eternal life so that's all I got anybody
else all right we're GNA leave it right
there we gonna keep moving sister
Deborah yes mure uh Malik mcure ask
Malik secure ask is it okay for a woman
to teach the word side by side with her
husband brother juliia share some light
on this side by side
wow that that's becoming a popular
question let's go to First Timothy
Chapter 2 let's look at the Bible let's
let the word of God give you an
answer again side by side and then where
you anyway side by side
where First Timothy 2 brother tenzel we
just G to read verse 11 and
12 1 Timothy 2 11 and 12
go ahead well let the woman learn in
silence without all subjection uhhuh
suffer not a woman to teach nor youur
authority over the man but to silent but
to be in
silence that's what the book says right
the Lord said do all things decent and
in order you cuz eventually you're going
to go somewhere before a pull pit and
that's how organization start
s our pastor and female pastors is
organization it is not scripture right
the Woman's Place is not in the pull pit
or and we just read what the book said
let the woman learn and S she could
learn some things she could teach a
younger children but to be side by side
with a husband I can't read that I can
read only this right
here he said but I suffer not a woman to
teach nor to usurp authority over the
man but to be in silence sometime they
people want to take it uh further than
that we going to end it right there what
the book say that's all I
got all right we'll leave it right there
as we continue to move with the time
check yes the time is
8:27 uh
commissioner Paula a
Sanford asks a female relative have
gotten serious about departing from
sexual sin now she understands the
seriousness of such she wants to know if
she can be
forgiven brother Dre what you
say let's go to Ezekiel 18 and we're
gonna read a couple of verses there and
we got one other place Ezekiel 18 and uh
read verses 21 and 22
brother go ahead when you get it but if
the w wied will turn from all his sins
that he have committed and keep all my
statutes and do that which is lawful and
right he shall surely live he should not
die all his transgression that he have
committed they should not be mentioned
unto him in his righteousness that he ha
done he shall live that's right so when
you turn from your sin your
transgressions that you have committed
the book says they shall not be
mentioned onto you right and you in the
righteousness that you walking in you
will live now let's go to acts the 2
chapter and we're GNA pick it up at
verse 36 Acts 2 and
36 when you get it go ahead
brother therefore let all the house of
Israel knoweth surely that God have made
that same Jesus whom you have crucified
both Lord and Christ so Peter gave the
breakdown
about know Jesus and he said let all the
house of Israel know that the same Jesus
that you have crucified is now both Lord
and Christ verse 37 go ahead brother now
when they heard this they were praked in
their heart and said unto Peter and to
the rest of the Apostles wom men and
Brethren what shall we do
then Peter said unto them repent and be
baptized every one of you in the name of
Jesus Christ for the remission of sins
ye shall receive the gift of the Holy
Ghost yeah repent turn away from the
behavior that you were doing before and
as you grow be baptized in this thing
know what you committing yourself to be
baptize in the name of the Lord Jesus
Christ for the remission of sins and you
will receive the gift of the Holy Ghost
continue for the promise is unto you and
to your children and to all that are far
off even as many as the Lord Our God
shall call verse 40 and that's it go
ahead and with many other words did he
testify and exort saying save yourselves
from this unto generation because this
generation is UN God they are are not
serving God so you have to deliver
yourself from this unto
Generation all right thank you for that
brother and uh we wish you the best in
your journey sister all right next
question yes to uh Tangela De
Jesus uh says a family member want to
attend a fam a family family member
wants to attend a family reunion they
want to bring prep food and teach family
about truth about Sabbath would they be
polluting
it all right guest caller can you share
some light on this question
here well the thing is is that they
bring prep food it depends on when they
prepared it if they prepared it uh uh uh
before the sun before uh uh the Sabbath
day came in like the book said you know
you SE what you will and bake what you
will before the Sabbath day and then you
can eat it on the Sabbath day it don't
matter where you eat it at as long as
you don't prepar on the Sabbath day so
uh it wouldn't be uh uh uh uh it
wouldn't be polluting the Sabbath to eat
anyway all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question there next
question we can talk right here says I
heard Jesus visit hell is if there is no
hell where did he go and what and to do
what so where did he go and to do what
if there is no hell all right well let's
talk right here about that question
guess caller
yeah you know the Lord uh uh uh the Lord
spoke about Israel in Isaiah the 5th I'm
going throw this in first and then I'm
going clear this up I think let's go
into Isaiah the 5th
chapter because when you start talking
hell you talking a state of condition
mhm and uh where told
uh Lord talking about the people that uh
uh that you know that's getting off in
the party and everything and and and uh
uh what happened is they don't pay no
attention to the word of
God I want to get Isaiah five and let's
see 14 13 or
14 not in verse 11 11 all right
woe unto them that rise up early in the
morning that they may follow strong dram
that continue unto night till wine
inflame
them and the harp and The Vow the tabd
and pip and wine are in their feasts but
they regard not the works of the Lord
neither consider the operation of his
hands therefore my people are gone into
captivity because they have no knowledge
and their Honorable Men are famished and
their multitudes dried up with thirst
therefore hell have enlarged herself and
opened her mouth without
measure and their glory and their
multitude and their PK and he that
rejoices shall descend into
it now if hell in this particular case
was the Lake of Fire that mean that all
Israel in the Lake of Fire is this
saying
Y and and and descended into and Hell
have enlarged itself right so know see
the condition and what it's and what
you're talking about when Jesus talk
when Jesus uh uh Jesus the hell he was
talking about was the grave because the
word hell is shuel and and he letting
you know that when he died he went into
the grave let's let me go and and and
show you on something on that right
quick let's go into
Psalms Let's uh uh let's go into Psalms
uh let's see the 16th chapter and read
from 8 to 10 Psalms 16 8
to10 read it when you get there I have
set the lord always before me because he
is at my right hand I shall not be moved
therefore my heart is glad and my glory
rejoiceth My Flesh also shall Rest In
Hope for thou will not leave my soul in
Hell neither will thou suffer thy Holy
One to see
corruption he said now his flesh going
to rest in Hope and uh uh uh because you
he not going to leave his Hol His Holy
One In Hell neither suffer his flesh to
seek corruption in in other words
decomposed so what he talking about here
is the
grave that is a state of condition and
look what he said concern on that same
order now go to Psalm the 30th chapter
and read verse 1
through3 Psalm 30th verses
1 through
3 I would extol thee Oh Lord for thou H
lifted up lifted me up and has not made
my foe to Rejoice over me oh Lord my God
I Cried unto thee and thou has healed me
oh Lord thou has brought up my soul from
the grave thou has kept me alive that I
should not go down to the
pit see so this case the the uh hell is
the grave because the word for for hell
is sh it's talking about the grave over
here
he said that
uh in uh uh Psalm
16 you know he said that uh uh uh he
will read bring his ho up out of hell
and over here in Psalm 30 he said he
would bring hiso his soul up out of the
Grave because they wanted the same if
Jesus didn't go to hell ain't no hell
ain't no l ofy and not going to be until
the Lord come leifi would be just
another state of condition
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question next
question next question KJ War's
explanation to 1 Corinthians 1 verse 21
the foolishness of preaching the
gospel all right brother Jerome share
some light on the foolishness of
preaching the
gospel well to those of us who got on
understanding the gospel ain't
foolishness to us but let me show you
who it is foolishness to because they
not spiritually discerned but the ones
that got their eyes on through the
spirit of the
Lord they know it's the power of God
unto salvation so let's go to read that
uh 21 then we going to skip up tzel read
that
21 what's the first Corinthians what was
the first Corinthians
yeah they wanted First Corinthians uh
one First Corinthians 1 verse 21
yes for after that in the wisdom of God
the World by wisdom you not God and it
pleased God by the foolishness of
preaching to save them that believe yeah
but skip up to verse 18 cuz the gospel
is not foolish is to us let me show you
who is foolishness to verse
18 for the preaching of the Cross is to
them that perish foolishness but unto us
which are saved it is the power of God
yeah that's it that's all I
got all right thank you for that as we
move on to our next one yes uh KJ also
ask for you to explain job 20 9 verse4
The Secret Of God upon my
Tabernacle all right let's go there
tenzel job 29 and4 The Secret Of God
upon my
Tabernacle because in this case job is
talking about his body when he speaks
about Tabernacle in this case Lord also
had the Tabernacle of the congregation
which is the tent where he used to
communicate with Moses but let's pick it
up at Job 29 And1 because job was in a
bad place
here go ahead and read
brother over job continued his Parable
and said oh thou were as in months past
as in the days when God preserved me
yes when his candle shine upon my head
and when by his light I walk through
Darkness
uhhuh as I was in the days of my youth
when the secret of God was upon my
Tabernacle yes when the secret of God
was upon my Tabernacle he talking about
when it was upon his body because job
was in a bad place here read that next
verse five when the almighty was yet
with me when my children were about me
and at this point all his children had
got killed and he got Afflicted and job
had a lot going on in his life but you
asked about this 29 and it's talking
about job's body here and let's go to
that second Peter 1 second Peter
1 and let's show that the
Tabernacle can also be called your body
second Peter
1 when you get there
brother let's pick it up at that verse
13 and 14 because this is
um Peter here talking go
ahead yeah I think it meat as long as I
am in this Tabernacle to stir you up by
putting you in remembrance so Peter was
saying here hey yet I think it me as
long as I am in this body to stir you up
and to put you in remembrance about this
word of God go ahead knowing that Surly
I must put
this my Tabernacle even as our Lord
Jesus Christ have showed me and so he
was saying knowing that surely I must
put off this my Tabernacle this this
Flesh and Blood body that he was in he's
saying hey because everybody's going to
share that and receive award done while
you was in this body so job was talking
about his body in that job 29 and verse
four and that's all I got anybody else
and we GNA keep it moving sister
Deborah yes uh a Thomas Wars you to
explain Lamentations 4: 7 and 8 and also
to explain how to rebuke Deuteronomy 12
vers 15 and 22 if used against the
dietary law and they also ask what is an
unclean person so the first one is
lamentation 47 and 8 let's go to that
Lamentations 47 and8 brother tanzel that
book right after
Jeremiah and when you get there brother
pick it up at that verse seven and the
guest caller take it from
there her na purer than snow they were
whiter than milk there were more Rudy in
in body than rubies their polishing was
as
Sapphire their V Vis is blacker than a
coold they are not known in the streets
their skin Cleaves to their bones it is
withered it has become like a
stick all they saying is there was
during the time when uh
uh when Nebuchadnezzar laid a
Siege to to Judah
and would let nobody come in and nobody
come out and so when he talking about
the nazarites these are the guys that
were special guys you know uh uh you
know that had made a vow to God anyway
it was telling these guys was clean but
ain't nobody's whiter than snow even the
Gentile but he saying that they was
clean but also too it's talking about
they vage was robust it was healthy see
say like and Ruddy and body Ruddy is a
brownish red but then it said then their
skin then their skin was was was black
as cold that's what happen when we get
the uh uh uh when when when people get
real sick black people and they uh and
they are uh uh under Seas what happened
is all all it's telling about is how
sick these guys look you know they lost
the natural
color and now they been in the famine so
long until uh uh there nothing but Skin
and Bones and the skin on us gets real
black when we get sick like that that's
all it's talking about the suffering of
the people under the uh uh seed that
Nebuchadnezzar had on Judah yes sir was
the all right and the next one was to
how to rebuke Deuteronomy
12 vers 15 and
22 if used against the dietary
law let's
go the best way to rebuke it is to go
and read it and see what it
says okay you said do the what now 12
vers 15 and
22 okay we're going to go and read this
because
uh people read this and say that the
Lord said that you can eat unclean food
but no it's not saying that no if you
PID some attention instead of trying to
distort the word of God you would see
that so this is 12 and we going to read
what was the first
one uh
15 Read verse 15 and we going to pay
attention to
it okay read it
see first first thing is this talking
about the Lord uh uh uh is having a
feast before your God in fact let's back
up before we get down
there let's back up to verse uh uh
uh
verse but when you come over Jordan but
what they really did first thing they
did when they came over Jordan was had
the Passover but goad
go ahead but when you go over Jordan and
dwell in the land which the Lord your
God giveth you to inherit and when he
giveth you rest from all your enemies
round about so that you dwell in
safety then there shall be a place which
the Lord your God shall choose to call
his name to dwell there thither shall ye
bring all that I command you your burnt
offerings and your sacrifice your tiing
and the heave offering of your of your
hand and all your choice vows which ye
vow all these took take place in the
feast when you keeping all the feast go
ahead you shall rejoice before the Lord
your God ye and your sons and your
daughters and your men servants and your
maid servants and the Levites that is
within your gates for as much as you
have no part no inheritance with
you he saiding in the place that he
he want to bring all your sacrifices
down and do
that and the Levites and your children
everybody supposed to come and these are
the feast he's talking about but keep on
reading take heed to thyself that thou
offer not thy burnt offer in every place
that thou see in other words you just
can't excuse me you just can't offer it
anywhere you have to offer where the
Lord tell you to offer we take that you
don't
put go ahead and read but in the place
which the Lord shall choose in one of
thy tribes there Thou shalt offer thy
burn offering and there Thou shalt do
all that I command
thee not
withstanding thou mayest kill and eat
flesh in all thy Gates whatsoever thy
Soul lusted after according to the
blessing of the Lord thy God which he
have given thee the
uncan pay attention he said but not
manding you can also uh uh kill and eat
flesh in your own gate that's at your
own house
okay and what he said now now this is
the part that they trying to
Dorey read that the
unclean the unclean and the clean may
eat thereof as of the road book and as
of the heart
now he said and the unclean and the
clean may eat thereof he didn't say the
clean and unclean may be
eaten right so the clean and unlean that
mean that you sister might be on a
monthly uh brother uh uh might have an
issue and he can't come to a particular
feast or he might have uh uh uh uh been
defiled by the dead and they come but he
can eat but if he do it and when you're
do it in your own house you can be clean
or unclean but the food you eating is
clean that have nothing to do with the
dietary law read that last one read it
one more
time not withstanding thou mayest kill
and eat flesh in all thy Gates
whatsoever thy Soul lusted after
according to the blessing of the Lord
thy God which he have given Thee the
unclean and the clean may eat thereof as
of the robe book and as of the
heart now did you see how clear it is
the unclean and the clean may eat
thereof he didn't say that you may eat
the clean and the unclean he said so the
ones that's doing the he so the
unclean person or the clean person can
eat of but they ain't got nothing
dietary law what was the next
verse 22
okay skip down and let's look at
it even as the Rob and the heart is
eaten so now I tell you what you do
start at
21 for this is the place that the Lord
choose if it's too far from you then you
got to you can do something with it go
ahead and read and if the place with the
Lord thy God have chosen to put his name
there be too far from thee then thou
shal kill of thy her and of thy flock
which the Lord hath given thee as I have
commanded thee and thou sht eat in thy
Gates whatsoever thou Soul lusted
after even as the RO buck and the heart
is eaten so Thou shalt eat them the
unclean and the clean shall eat of them
alike what who who shall eat of them can
eat of them the
person there you go the unclean person
and the clean person might eat thereof
it's not saying that you may eat the
clean and unclean what he saying is if
you are unclean like I said ear you're
defiled by a dead body woman on a Monday
brother have an
issue still you can
eat of this uh feast in your
Gates but you ain't no condition you can
Fe eat eat uh uh uh uh clean or unclean
because the Lord said don't do that we
going to go to one more place let's go
to Leviticus 11th
chapter and we're going to read verse
25 read
it and whosoever beareth all of the
carcass of them shall wash his clothes
and be unclean until the evening
that Leviticus 11 and
25 okay maybe uh uh uh let's let's look
at it maybe I
just maybe I'm sorry maybe Leviticus
20 Leviticus 20 because this is the
thing that the Lord has done and we got
to adhere to
it let's see Leviticus
20 20 and
25 uh uhhuh okay 20 and 25 I'm sorry go
ahead and read it ye shall therefore put
difference between clean beast and
unclean and between unclean fouls and
clean and ye shall not make your souls
abominable by beasts or by fouls or by
any manner of living thing that creepeth
from the ground which I have separated
from you as
unclean so the Lord is the one that
separated you as
unclean so what what they what we're
saying in dter is that the unclean and
the clean person may eat of these clean
beast that's all I have to say all right
thank you for that hope that answers
your question sister Deborah time is a
ticking
uh yes byan asked is Elijah one of the
two witnesses mentioned in Revelation 11
uh verse three they also gave
Mel Malachi 3 verse1 and Luke 1 verse1
17 well Jerome what you
say uh absolutely not Elijah is not one
of the two witnesses and and uh we
understand when you read that
Revelations that the two witnesses are
going to be
killed right Elijah not even gonna be
around when that take place right and
then Elijah comes up in the first
resurrection he he gonna
be God you know so he certainly won't be
killed when he become God when he come
up in that first resurrection but let's
go read those verses Revelations uh 11
and3 and I will give power unto my two
witnesses and they shall prophesy as
1,23 score days clothed in
sackcloth uh skip down and read verse
seven and
8 and when they shall have finish their
testimony the the Beast that ascended
out of the bottom his pit shall make war
against them and shall overcome them and
kill them see those two witnesses going
to be killed so they can't be Elijah
because Elijah gonna be in the grave
when this take place until the first
resurrection right okay let's go read
the other one Malachi 3
And1 go
ahead you got it
okay I was send my messengers he shall
prepare the way before me and the Lord
whom ye seek shall suddenly come to his
Temple even the messenger of the
Covenant whom you Delight in behold he
shall come sayeth the Lord of
hosts yeah
so even if you think that's John the
Baptist is actually the Lord that's
going to suddenly come into His Temple
he the messenger of the Covenant but is
he is the two witnesses ain't Jesus nor
is it John the Baptist John the Baptist
he going to be still in the
grave when them two witnesses get killed
too until the first resurrection in the
last place there that Luke 1 and 17 Luke
1 and
[Applause]
17 he shall go before him in the spirit
and power of el lias to turn the hearts
of the father to the children and the
disobedient to the wisdom of the just to
make ready a people prepared for the
Lord and I'm imagining that you
referring to this verse as being John
the Baptist okay but like I said earlier
he gonna be in a grave when the two
witnesses get
killed and he going to come up in the
first
resurrection right speaking about John
the Baptist that's that's all I
got all right hope that answer that
question next
question yes by ran Israel also asks
what is the difference between the
cherim's four wings and sarim six wings
in Ezekiel 10 verse 21 and Isaiah 6
verse
two all right so what's the difference
in the four WI the six wings yes caller
let's go to that uh Ezekiel 10 and 21
and read it when you get there brother
Tan on the guest caller take it from
there Ezekiel 10 and verse
21 Ezekiel 10 and
21 yes
sir everyone have four faces of peace
and everyone four wings and the likeness
of the hand of a man was under their
wings now the first thing is it's the uh
uh he said and and this is the hope when
it com to the number of wings this is a
typ of in in in Ezekiel but if we go
into Ezekiel the first chapter and read
it carefully we will see the six wings
back up to Ezekiel the first
chapter and we going to take our time
and examine the uh uh uh the 11
verse Ezekiel 1 And1 we're going to
examine
it so when you get there start
it thus were their faces and their wings
were stretched
upward now let me text up now you said
this uh uh uh wings were stretched
upward this is two Wings stretched
upward go
ahead two wings of everyone were joined
one to another and two Wings everyone
was joined one to another go
ahead and two covered their body and two
covered their bodies how many is
that six
six that's six wings now to show you
now there is no difference and and
there's no they call zap and Isaiah but
they are cheram because these was around
God everywhere he went and to show you
what I'm talking about let's go into
revelation we going to go into
Revelation the 5th chapter and read
verse
8 and when he had taken the book The
Four beasts and the four and 20 Elders
fell down before the lamb having every
one of them hars and golden vowels full
of OD which are the prayers of saints
oh and they sung a new song saying thou
are worthy to take the book and to open
the seals thereof no is this Revelation
5 and8 I mean uh four I'm sorry
Revelation 4 and8 my mistake four and
eight and the four beasts had each of
them six wings about him and they were
full of eyes within and they rest not
day and night saying holy holy holy Lord
God Almighty which was and is and is to
come not he the same for be same H Sher
of
angels assure you that the that the Sher
of angels because these are the ones
that the Lord put around him in Adam's
day let's go into Genesis the 3 chapter
and read verse 22 and
24 read it when you get
there and Adam called
uh Genesis 3 and 24 right yeah so he
drove out the man and placed at the east
of the Garden of Eden CHS and a flaming
sword was turned every way to keep the
way of the Tree of Life
now and uh they keep the way of Tree of
Life go
ahead that that was it what did he put
around what did he put around
him is that correct yep y that mean he
wherever he go the Cher Angel was there
now go to uh uh they going to go one
last place 99th Psalm 19 19 uh 99th
chapter Psalm and read one
verse read it when you get
there which uh which verse you want me
to
read all right verse one the Lord reth
let the people tremble he sth between
the chairs let the Earth be
move okay now that's why when they build
a temple they had them Cher up angels on
each side of the mercy SE they know such
thing as a Ser for him that's that's a
uh that's a it's just like they talk in
one part of the book they might call
some call it submiss but you know that
it's talking about one H type of Angel
that's a cherup angel that's the type of
angel that Satan is so it's sarif him
you haven't seen it no place else
it should have been chair bam and all of
them had six wings that's all I have to
say all right we thank you for that hope
that answered their question sister
Deborah time Che yes the time is
9:04 well our show has come to an end we
want to thank everybody from all around
the world who tuned in with us we took
joy and taking part in answering your
questions we know that you submitted
some questions that we didn't have a
chance to get to but please don't
resubmit them sister Deborah's going to
take what you submitted put it in
rotation and we will deal with that
question next Wednesday at the same time
so we thank you all and until we all
come together again be safe out there be
blessed and may the Lord have mercy on
us all close us out brother
tanzel Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven
give us this day our daily bread and
forgive us of our debts as we forgive
our debt to us and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen amen amen good night